Alvieto Haykal

Surabaya, Indonesia | haykalcs@gmail.com | (62) 822-3489-7335 linkedin.com/in/alvietomhf | alvietomhf.github.io

Fullstack Developer

A skilled, competent, and diligent individual, specializing in the fullstack web development (Laravel/CI - NodeJS/Express/Nest - ReactJS/Next). For the last 3 years, I have been developing applications using PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript & Go programming languages. I love coding and am interested in solving problems while coding. I've hands on in all stages of the programming cycle, from planning to development and deployment. No two days are the same for me; my tasks may involve analyzing algorithms, altering code, fixing bugs, brainstorming ideas for integrating new systems.

Experience

Web Developer, PT Bimasakti Multi Sinergi (Sept 2022 - present)

- Maintain and develop features SpeedCash
 - o API forwarder for reporting, inquiry and payment
 - o UBP (Utility bill payment), SpeedCash Poin
 - Landing page, dashboard member
 - KYC verification
 - Bulk transfer internal
 - Firebase notification sender
- Maintain and develop features TiketKAI
 - Update payment method using payment gateway
 - Integration with biller for booking and payment
 - Backoffice application
- Maintain and develop features Micrommerce
 - Authentication with OTP
 - Product management
 - o Order management
 - Cashout management
 - Integration with rajaongkir
 - o Integration with linked account SpeedCash
 - Chat module using XMPP instant messaging

Backend Developer, Runshop (Aug 2021 - Jan 2022)

- · Integration with H2H provider
- Integration with payment gateway
- Develop bank mutation checker
- Develop scrapper payment
- Develop notification service

Backend Developer, PT Kipa Teknologi Indonesia (Jan 2021 – Feb 2021) Internship

Develop a project called "Sadean" including:

- Authentication module using JWT
- Customer management
- Product management
- Notification module for sending email and firebase push notification

Skills

- Laravel/CI (Expert)
- NodeJS/Express/Nest (Expert)
- ReactJS/Next (Expert)
- Redis/Memcached (Expert)
- Go (Intermediate)
- RabbitMQ/Kafka (Intermediate)
- PHP, JavaScript/TypeScript (Expert)
- HTML, CSS (Expert)
- MySQL, PostgreSQL (Expert)
- Docker (Intermediate)
- GitHub, Gitlab CI/CD (Intermediate)

Certifications

• Backend Developer Expert (Dicoding Indonesia, 2021)

Education

• Universitas Negeri Surabaya, Teknik Informatika (2018 - 2022)

Languages

- English Fluent
- Bahasa Indonesia Native